I've created almost 25,000 images with
我用 Midshine 创建了近 25,000 张图片
Midshine, so I know the tool pretty
，所以我对这个工具非常了解
well. Today, I want to talk about the
。 今天，我想谈谈
Mid Churnney editor. It has been around
Mid Churnney 编辑器。 这项功能已经存在
for a while, but now you can also work
一段时间了，但现在你也可以使用
with layers. That's very
图层了。 那非常
useful. I tested the editor from a
有用。 我从初学者的角度测试了这款编辑器，
beginner's view and tried many different
并尝试了很多不同的
things.
功能。
I'll show you step by step how it works.
我会一步一步地向你展示它是如何运作的。
If you want to further customize images
如果您想在 MidJourney 中进一步自定义图像
in MidJourney, then you've come to the
，那么您来对
right place because the editor in
地方了，因为 MidJourney 中的编辑器
Midjourney is exactly the right solution
正是为此而设的
for this. There are actually two of
。 实际上有两个
them. One can be found on the left in
。 您可以在左侧导航栏中找到它
the navigation. This is the so-called
。 这就是所谓的
external image editor. If I click on it,
外部图像编辑器。 如果我点击它，
I am redirected to the edit your images
就会跳转到编辑图片
page. Assuming you haven't worked with
页面。 假设您之前没有使用过此功能
it yet, you will initially only see this
，您最初只会看到“
edit new image section. If you click on
编辑新图像”部分。 点击后
it, you now have the option of either
，您可以选择
using images from a URL or uploading
使用来自 URL 的图片或
images from an external source. If we
从外部来源上传图片。 如果
want to use the URL, simply rightclick
要使用 URL，只需右键
on an image of your choice and then
单击您选择的图片，然后
click on copy image URL under share and
单击“分享”下的“复制图片 URL”并
save. Then simply return to the edit
保存即可。 然后只需返回到
from URL input mask and then paste the
URL 输入框进行编辑，并将
link you just copied there. Midjourney
刚刚复制的链接粘贴到那里即可。  Midjourney
will then use exactly this image here.
将会使用此处所示的这张图片。
The second way to activate the external
激活外部
image editor is as already mentioned
图像编辑器的第二种方法是前面提到的
this brown button. This allows you to
这个棕色按钮。 这样就可以
select an image from your hard disk. But
从硬盘中选择图像了。 但
there is actually a third way to edit
实际上还有第三种编辑
images. Simply click on an image of your
图像的方法。 只需点击您
choice and you will see the
选择的图片，您就会
inconspicuous edit button at the bottom
在右下角看到不显眼的编辑按钮
right. Now it may be that this is not
。 现在，
visible for you. This is probably
您可能看不到这一点。 这可能是
because you have not yet activated its
因为您尚未
visibility via more options and more
通过更多选项和操作来启用其可见性
actions. If I uncheck the box, you can
。 如果我取消勾选这个复选框，你可以
see what happens. This means simply
看到会发生什么。 这意味着只需
click on more options and place a red
点击更多选项，然后
check mark next to more actions. Then
在“更多操作”旁边打上红色勾号即可。 然后
simply click on edit. Now we are in the
只需点击编辑即可。 现在我们进入了
internal image editor. Confusing a
内部图像编辑器。 有点令人困惑
little. This internal editor is used as
。 顾名思义，这个内部编辑器
the name suggests to modify images
用于修改
created purely via midjourney. We also
完全通过 midjourney 创建的图像。 我们还可以
find the normal standard functions in
在右上角找到常用的标准功能
the top right hand corner. More on this
。
in a moment. What is different here
稍后会详细说明。
however is the vary function and the
但不同之处在于 vary 功能和
editor actions field. There we find the
编辑器操作字段。 在那里我们可以找到
open and edit tab button. In short,
打开和编辑标签页的按钮。 简而言之，
clicking on it triggers the same action
点击它会触发
as clicking on edit in the navigation on
与点击左侧导航栏中的“编辑”相同的操作
the left. But now let's work with the
。 但现在让我们使用功能
more versatile tool, the external image
更强大的工具——外部图像
editor. To do this, click on edit in the
编辑器。 要进行此操作，请点击
navigation on the left. Then click on
左侧导航栏中的“编辑”。 然后点击
edit new image. And now I select the
编辑新图像。 现在我选择
brown edit uploaded image field to edit
棕色的“编辑已上传图像”字段来编辑
an image. I've already prepared
图像。 我已经为此做好了准备
something for this. This blurred
。 这张背景模糊的
background image. The two tabs edit and
图片。 这里，“编辑”和“
retexture are crucial here. Both
重新贴图”这两个标签至关重要。 这两个
functions are fundamentally different.
功能本质上是不同的。
With edit you can edit images just like
使用编辑功能，您可以像
in a graphics program. With retexture
在图形程序中一样编辑图像。 通过重新贴图，
you can change the style and color of
您可以改变图像的样式和颜色，
images i.e their entire
即改变图像的整个
substance. Step one is the edit
内容。 第一步是编辑
function. The tools that we see directly
功能。 下面这些工具在
below become relevant when we have
我们
already executed a task. More on this in
已经执行完任务后才会派上用场。 稍后会详细说明
a moment. The first tool is called move
。 第一个工具叫做移动
and resize. If you activate this
和调整大小。 启用此
function, the image will have a white
功能后，图像的每个角都会出现一个白色
handle in each corner. If I move one of
手柄。 按住鼠标按钮并移动其中一个
these white fields while holding down
白色区域
the mouse button, I can reduce or
，就可以缩小或
enlarge the image. The other alternative
放大图像。 另一种方法
is this slider on the left, you can use
是使用左侧的滑块，您可以
it to change images by percentage. A pro
按百分比更改图像。 这里给个专业
tip at this point, don't reduce the
建议，不要把
image too much because the smaller the
图像缩小太多，因为
image is, the wilder midjourneys
图像越小，旅途中的各种
interpretations become. Stay roughly in
解读就越离谱。 大致保持在与
the same range as what you see here. You
此处所示范围相同的范围内。 您
can simply grab the image and move it to
可以直接抓住图像，并将其移动到
canvas. You can also change the aspect
画布内您选择的位置。 您也可以在
ratio here. I reset the entire
这里更改宽高比。 我暂时把所有东西都重新布置了一遍
arrangement for now. For example, you
。 例如，您
can change the canvas size to 3x4, 2x3,
可以将画布尺寸更改为 3x4、2x3、16x9
16x9, or
或
9x6. And of course, you can use the
9x6。 当然，您也可以
slider again to adjust the image scale.
再次使用滑块来调整图像比例。
By the way, more than 100% is not
顺便说一句，超过100%是
possible. In this tutorial, we will
不可能的。 在本教程中，我们
initially stick to the standard format
首先将采用标准的
of 16x9. Incidentally, you can see that
16x9 格式。 顺便一提，您可以看到
the tools below edit have now been
下面的编辑工具现在已经
activated. These are undo or redo or
激活了。 这些操作包括撤销、重做或
reset. I can use undo to go back step by
重置。 我可以使用撤销功能，一步一步地返回
step to the activities I've carried out
到我目前为止执行过的操作
so far. Redo is self-explanatory. With
。 重做功能无需解释。
reset, I return to the original state of
重置后，图像将恢复到原始状态
the image. If we next look at the paint
。 接下来我们看一下绘图
tool, we find two editing options, erase
工具，会发现有两个编辑选项：擦除
and restore. Below this, I can define
和恢复。 在此下方，我可以定义
the brush size. If you look at the
画笔大小。 如果你仔细观察
image, you will see this slightly
图片，你会看到这个略微
transparent circle. This is the size of
透明的圆圈。 这是
your brush. I can not only reduce or
你的刷子的大小。 我不仅可以
enlarge it with the mouse wheel, but
用鼠标滚轮缩小或放大它，
also with the slider on the left.
还可以用左侧的滑块进行调整。
Another pro tip, always make the brush
另一个专业技巧是，始终将画笔
slightly larger so that you give
稍微大一些，这样可以让
midjourney the freedom to interpret the
midjourney 更自由地诠释
image better. If I now mark an area with
图像。 如果我现在用橡皮擦标记一个区域
erase, for example, these flags here,
，例如这里的这些标记，
and then click on restore, you will see
然后点击恢复，您将
a shadow of the original image in the
在背景中看到原始图像的阴影
background. You now have the option of
。 您现在可以进一步
refining your selection. To do this,
筛选您的选择。 要做到这一点，
simply reduce the brush size slightly
只需稍微缩小画笔大小，
and remove what you have already
然后删除你已经
selected. If I now click on submit edit,
选中的部分即可。 如果我现在点击提交编辑，
MidJourney is instructed to only make
MidJourney 将被指示只对
changes in the area you have selected.
您选择的区域进行更改。
Let me first reset the entire setup via
让我先通过重置来恢复整个设置
reset. I'll show you the smart select
。 我稍后会向您展示智能选择
function in a moment. First, let's jump
功能。 首先，我们直接进入
to the layers topic. You'll find this at
图层主题。 您可以在左下角找到它
the bottom left. As the term suggests,
。 顾名思义，
you can place different layers on top of
你可以像在 Photoshop 中一样，将不同的图层放置在
each other, just like in Photoshop, for
彼此之上
example. I've tested this extensively
。 我进行了大量测试
and found that it actually works very
，发现使用
well with one to two layers. If there
一到两层效果非常好。 如果
are several layers, midjourney still has
存在多个层级，那么在旅途中仍然会遇到
a bit of a problem. So, what exactly can
一些问题。 那么，
you do here? Simply click on the word
你在这里究竟可以做什么呢？ 只需点击“
add and upload an external image. I
添加”字样，然后上传外部图片即可。 我
select an image from my external hard
从外置硬盘中选择一张图片，
disk and add it to my composition as a
并将其作为第二层添加到我的作品中
second layer, so to speak. This image of
。 这张企鹅的图片
a single penguin is now in front of my
现在位于我的
background image and is marked red as
背景图片前面，
active at the bottom left. You can
左下角标有红色，表示处于活动状态。 您可以
select the individual layers at any time
随时选择单个图层
and delete them again. The one marked in
并将其删除。 红色标记的部分正在
red is currently being edited. By using
编辑中。 借助
this image of the penguin, I can now
这张企鹅图片，我现在可以
explain the smart select tool very well.
很好地解释智能选择工具了。
Here we find the include and exclude
这里我们找到了包含和排除
functions. If I select include and click
函数。 如果我选择“包含”并
on the penguin with the left mouse
用鼠标左键单击企鹅
button, midjourney recognizes the figure
，midjourney 会识别该图形
and marks it with this green
并用绿色
hatching. Exclude removes selected areas
阴影线标记它。 排除功能会再次移除选定的区域
again. That was step one. Now you can
。 这是第一步。 现在您可以
use erase selection to delete the active
使用“擦除选区”功能
selection from the image. In other
从图像中删除当前选区。
words, cut a hole in the image or use
换句话说，在图像上挖个洞，或者使用
erase background to remove the area that
擦除背景功能去除
is now not highlighted in green. This is
现在没有绿色高亮显示的区域。 这
exactly the inverse effect. However, we
正是相反的效果。 但是，我们
want the figure to remain and only the
希望保留人物形象，只
background to be removed. That's why I
去除背景。 所以我才
click on erase background here.
点击这里的“擦除背景”。
Incidentally, if you have made a
顺便一提，如果您犯了错误
mistake, you can use the undo and redo
，您可以随时使用撤销和重做
functions at any time and go back step
功能，一步一步地撤销操作
by step. The penguin is still layer 1.
。 企鹅仍然是第一层，
The background is layer two. On the far
背景是第二层。 最
right, we see the basic element, the
右边是基本元素，即
original image. If we now combine the
原始图像。 如果我们现在将
individual tools with each other, for
各个工具结合起来，
example, move and resize, then I can
例如移动和调整大小，那么我可以将
move the penguin to a different position
企鹅移动到
in the image. Now, the actual
图像中的不同位置。 现在，真正的
modification process begins. To do this,
修改过程开始了。 为此，
I go to layer 2, the background image,
我进入图层 2（背景图像），
and select the erase function. What I'm
然后选择擦除功能。 我
about to show you is crucial. You have
接下来要展示的内容至关重要。 你
to give MidJourney the option of
必须允许 MidJourney 将这
blending the two layers into each other.
两个图层混合在一起。
To do this, I take the brush and erase
为此，我用画笔擦除
the two objects. In this specific case,
两个对象过渡处的图像内容。 在这个具体例子中，
I want the transition between the
我希望
penguin and the background to be nicely
企鹅和背景之间的过渡能够
interpolated by midjourney. If I've
通过 midjourney 进行平滑的插值。 如果我
inadvertently performed a wrong action,
不小心执行了错误操作，
I can either click undo or use restore.
我可以点击撤销或使用还原功能。
Then I can remove what I have marked
这样我就可以删除我标记
incorrectly.
错误的内容了。
Next, I add the prompt a penguin looks
接下来，我在命令栏顶部添加提示“企鹅看起来很
amazed to the top of the command bar and
惊讶”，
then click on submit edit. Midjourney
然后点击提交编辑。  Midjourney
now leaves the basic structure with the
现在保留了包含
individual layers. If I click on the
各个图层的基本结构。 如果我
basic element on the top right again, I
再次点击右上角的基本元素，我
can change my entire job again, even
可以再次更改我的整个工作，
though midjourney is already working on
即使 midjourney 已经在处理
the new job. This means that whatever is
新工作了。 这意味着
outlined in red at the top right is
右上角红色框线框内的内容将在
shown here as an enlarged image. I now
此处以放大图像的形式显示。 我现在从这
select one of these four pictures. It is
四张图片中选择一张。 它
outlined in red at the top right and
在右上角用红色勾勒出来，并在
displayed here in large. Midjourney has
这里以大图显示。  Midjourney
now perfectly modeled the penguin into
已经完美地将企鹅融入
the background without you having to do
背景中，无需您进行
any major editing. By the way, if you
任何重大编辑。 顺便说一句，如果你
have to stop working on a current
不得不停止当前
project, you don't need to worry that
项目的工作，你不必担心
everything is gone. Midjourney saves the
所有成果都会丢失。 旅程中途保存了
log. Simply restart the application. Go
日志。 只需重启应用程序即可。 转到
to edit and you will find your last
编辑菜单，您会在“最近使用”下方找到您最后
edited file there under recent. It's as
编辑的文件。 就这么
simple as that. Then just click on it
简单。 然后
again and all the elements are there
再次点击，所有元素就会
again. So nothing has disappeared. Of
再次出现。 所以什么都没消失。
course I can still go backwards and
当然，我仍然可以前后穿梭
forwards. Everything you have done and
。 你所做的一切以及
all the images are still there. Now
所有的照片都还在那里。 现在
let's continue to change this picture
我们继续改变这幅图
here. To do this, I'll choose an image
。 为此，我将从
from the four suggestions that I like
四个建议的图片中选择我
best. I'll take this one. By the way,
最喜欢的一张。 我选这个。 顺便说一下，
you can see that this picture is new and
你可以看到这张图片是新生成的，
has no further layers. Please don't
没有其他图层。 请不要将
confuse the two. Next, I select move and
两者混淆。 接下来，我再次选择移动和
resize again and place the image in the
调整大小，并将图像缩小后放置在
middle at a reduced size. Again,
中间。 再次
remember not to reduce the image too
提醒，不要把图像缩小
much. Midjourney remains very
太多。  Midjourney 仍然非常
unconventional and could simply insert
规，如果给予它过多的自由，它可能会直接
something unwanted into the image if it
在图像中插入一些不想要的东西
has too much leeway. I press submit edit
。 我再次点击提交编辑，出现了
again with the same prompt. Of course, I
同样的提示。 当然，我也
could have written a different request.
可以写一份不同的请求。
with my prompt. Midjourney now expands
按照我的提示。 简而言之，Midjourney 现在会向
the image on all sides and performs a
各个方向扩展图像，并执行
zoom effect to put it bluntly. If we
缩放效果。 如果我们
click again on the basic element, this
再次点击基本元素，这
was our source image. That's where I
就是我们的源图像。 我
basically assembled the entire scene.
基本上就是在那里把整个场景搭建起来的。
Then I took this picture and in the
然后我拍了这张照片，在
latest version, I have a somewhat
最新版本中，我
wide-angle shot. Of course, it's clear
拍摄了一张广角照片。 当然，很显然，
that not all pictures are perfect.
并非所有照片都是完美的。
That's why MidJourney gives you four
这就是为什么 MidJourney 为您提供了四种选择方案的原因
alternatives to choose from. This
。 这张
picture already looks quite good and so
照片看起来已经很不错了，所以
you can gradually refine your image. In
你可以逐步完善它。 在
this picture, the penguin is standing on
这张照片中，企鹅站在
a small hill. I actually like that very
一个小山坡上。 我其实很喜欢那个
much. And now comes the part that makes
。 现在到了让
midjourney quite
旅途中段变得非常
extraordinary. But before we go any
特别的部分。 但在
deeper, here's another pro tip. When you
深入探讨之前，这里还有一条专业建议。 当你
found a picture you like, always
找到喜欢的图片时，一定要
remember to mark it so that it is
记得标记它，以便它能以
displayed large and then save it via
大图显示，然后通过
upscale to gallery. If you don't do
放大保存到图库。 如果您不这样做
this, your image will not be transferred
，您的图像将不会传输
to your normal midjourney gallery. You
到您常用的旅程中图库。 你
could also download images directly from
也可以直接从
the editor, but I always go the way via
编辑器下载图片，但我总是选择通过
upscale. But now back to the very
放大的方式来下载。 但现在让我们回到这个非常
special part. This is a really powerful
特别的部分。
feature if you know how to use it. You
如果你知道如何使用，这将是一个非常强大的功能。 你
can add incredible depth to your image.
可以为你的图片增添惊人的景深。
How does it work? Select one of your
它是如何运作的？
images in the editor. Reduce its size.
在编辑器中选择一张图片。 缩小它的尺寸。
Place it in the middle. And now comes
把它放在中间。 现在到了
personalization. In the top right hand
个性化定制的激动人心的时刻。
corner of the editor, there is this P
编辑器右上角有一个 P
symbol which stands for
符号，代表
personalization. Click on it and switch
个性化。 点击它并
on the function. This basically
开启该功能。 这基本上就
activates it yet without further
激活了它，但没有进一步的
specifications. Now select a mood board
说明。 现在选择一个
that you particularly like. I use faces
你特别喜欢的灵感板。 我喜欢用
colorful. You could also combine several
色彩鲜艳的面孔。 你也可以将几种
styles with each other, but this will
风格混合在一起，但这
eventually become a huge mishmash with
最终会变成一团乱麻，
no clear
没有清晰的
identification. You can see that
区分。
personalization is active by the red P
通过红色的 P 符号可以看出个性化设置已启用
symbol. Now midjourney knows I have to
。 现在 midjourney 知道我需要将
transfer the selected style to the new
选定的样式转移到新
image. Now I click on submit edit again.
图像上。 现在我再次点击提交修改。
For this example, I have slightly
在这个例子中，我对
modified the prompt. The changes relate
提示信息稍作修改。 这些变化
exclusively to the gray area marked here
仅与图中标记的灰色区域有关
in the image. Now we can see the result.
。 现在我们可以看到结果了。
Midjourney leaves the original style in
Midjourney 保留了中心的原始风格，
the center and generates a new theme
并生成了一个与您选择的
that matches the style of the mood board
情绪板风格相匹配的新主题
you have selected. Midjourney also
。  Midjourney 还
ensures that the two images are blended
确保两幅图像
into one another. This allows you to
相互融合。 这样你就可以
create completely new scenes. Of course,
创建全新的场景。 当然，
I can resize the output and write a
我可以调整输出大小并编写
different prompt. for example, trees and
不同的提示符。 例如，树木和
orcs. Erase the current profile and then
兽人。 删除当前配置文件，然后
select a new style from your mood
从您的灵感板中选择一种新风格
boards. For example, cool guy. And now
。 例如，很酷的人。
in the next step, midjourney adds the
接下来，midjourney 将
new style of the second mood board into
第二个情绪板的新风格添加到
the scene. Here is one last test again
场景中。 这是最后一次测试，这次的
prompt. I simply write another prompt
提示不同。 我只需写另一个提示，
and select the flower details mood
然后选择花卉细节情绪
board. Unfortunately, you can't see
板。 遗憾的是，你无法看到
which style is hidden behind which mood
哪个风格隐藏在哪个情绪
board's name. You either have to
板的名称背后。 你要么得
memorize the styles, which is most
记住这些样式，但这
likely not possible in most cases, or
在大多数情况下几乎不可能，要么就得靠
it's a bit of guesswork. And again, the
猜。 画面再次
image has changed. Don't forget to
发生了变化。
deactivate personalization again if you
如果您不再想使用个性化设置，请不要忘记再次将其停用
no longer want to use it. If I want to
。 如果我想
see what I've already edited in the
查看我在编辑器中已经编辑过的内容
editor, I click on view all in the top
，我会点击左上角的“查看全部”
leftand corner. This takes me to the
。 这会把我带到我
already familiar edit your images page.
已经很熟悉的“编辑图片”页面。   在
Here I can select all the images I have
这里，我可以按住鼠标左键选择我创建的所有图像，
button and then hide them using more and
然后使用“更多”和“隐藏”来隐藏它们
hide. If you want to delete your job
。 如果要将工作
completely in the editor, simply click
在编辑器中彻底删除，只需点击图像
on the small dust bin icon on the right
右侧的小垃圾桶图标即可
of the image. Now you can restart from
。 现在你可以从头
the beginning. The images which I
开始。 我
transferred via upscale to gallery can
通过高清放大功能上传到图库的图片
now be found in the overview section.
现在可以在概览部分找到。
Let's now have a look at the retexture
现在让我们来看看
function in step two. To do this, click
第二步中的重新贴图功能。 要做到这一点，请点击
on the retexture tab on the right. We
右侧的“重新贴图”选项卡。
will ignore the rest for this test. At
本次测试我们将忽略其余部分。
this point, it is important to think
此时此刻，发挥创造性思维至关重要
creatively. For example, enter knitted
。 例如，输入“针织
penguin and then click on submit
企鹅”，然后点击“提交
retexture. This will produce the
重新贴图”。 这将产生
following results. Pay attention to the
以下结果。 注意
flags and the figures in the background.
背景中的旗帜和人物。   在
Here we see the free interpretation of
这里，我们看到了对
midjourney which visualized a knitted
旅程中途的自由诠释，它将
depiction from your 3D rendering. This
你的 3D 渲染图可视化为针织图案。 这样会
produces results like this or something
产生类似这样的结果
similar. Again, remember to transfer the
。 再次提醒，请记得通过“上传图片到图库”的方式，将
image you like to your create profile
你喜欢的图片上传到你的个人资料
via upscale to gallery. Of course, you
页面。 当然，你
can also refine this further. To do
还可以进一步完善它。
this, click on edit again, then open in
为此，请再次单击“编辑”，然后在“
edit tab and load an external image.
编辑”选项卡中打开并加载外部图像。
Interestingly, cropped images such as
有趣的是，裁剪后的图片，例如
PNG files work very well. Then you no
PNG 文件，效果非常好。 这样您就
longer need to use the smart select
不再需要使用智能选择
function. You can see the cropped
功能了。 这里可以看到裁剪过的
penguin here. Place it in the position
企鹅图片。 将其放置在
of your choice and start modeling. This
您选择的位置，然后开始建模。 这
is now the older brother of the knitted
是针织企鹅的哥哥
penguin. Remember to erase the area
。 请记住擦除
between the two layers in the background
背景图像中两个图层之间的区域，
image so that MidJourney can blend the
以便 MidJourney 可以
two layers seamlessly. Again, it worked
无缝地混合这两个图层。 再次强调，它完全
perfectly without you having to use any
无需使用任何
other software. Both penguins now have
其他软件即可完美运行。 在相同的光照条件下，两只企鹅现在都呈现出各自
their very own look and feel in the same
独特的外观和感觉
lighting. The job is done. It's that
。 任务完成了。 就这么
simple. Don't overload the editor with
简单。 不要在编辑器中添加
too many layers. Midjourney may become a
过多图层。 旅途中可能会感到
little overwhelmed. I have been working
有些不知所措。 我使用
with Photoshop for about 25 years.
Photoshop 已有大约 25 年的时间。
MidJourney still has a long way to go if
MidJourney
it wants to compete with Photoshop. For
要想与Photoshop竞争，还有很长的路要走。
example, you can't mirror images at all
例如，你根本无法镜像图像，
and many other basic functions don't
许多其他基本功能也无法
work. Think more in terms of how you can
使用。 多想想如何将
combine two images together. Then the
两张图片结合起来。 那么
success rate is much
成功率就会
higher. That's it for this tutorial. I
高得多。 本教程到此结束。
hope you enjoyed it. Please leave a
希望你喜欢。 请点
like, subscribe to the channel, and
赞、订阅频道并
recommend it to others. Thank you very
推荐给其他人。 非常感谢您的
much for listening. See you soon. Your
聆听。 再见。 您的
channel AI. Now you know.
频道 AI。 现在你知道了。